Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
George McTurnan Kahin papers, ca. 1945-2000
14-27-3146
George McTurnan Kahin
77.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, clippings, manuscripts, documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, Cornell lectures and course materials, articles and speeches, files about meetings, and book draft.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of International Studies. George McTurnan Kahin graduated from Harvard University in 1940 and completed graduate work at Stanford University and Johns Hopkins University. He served in the Army during World War II, and lived in Indonesia from 1948-1949, during the peak of Indonesia's war for independence. He came to Cornell in 1951 as an assistant professor of government and executive director of the newly formed Southeast Asia Program. He served as director of the program until 1970, and also founded the Cornell Modern Indonesia Project in 1954, and directed it until his retirement in 1988.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, Cornell lectures and course materials, articles and speeches, files about meetings, and book draft.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kahin, George McTurnan.; Cornell University. Southeast Asia Program.; Cornell University. Modern Indonesia Project.; Cornell University. Dept. of Government.; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975.
Places:
Indonesia--Study and teaching.; United States--Foreign relations--Vietnam.; Vietnam--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Foreign relations--Indonesia.; Indonesia--Foreign relations--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of donor until 2026.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Book Manuscript
Box 1
Series II. Subject Files
Boxes 1-2, 76, 78
Series III. Correspondence
Boxes 2-10, 16-21, 37-44, 76
Series IV. Teaching and Research Materials
Boxes 10-13
Series V. Speeches and Meetings
Boxes 13-15, 78
Series VI. Lectures
Boxes 56-57
Series VII. Administration
Boxes 45-48
Series VIII. Indonesia and Research Materials
Boxes 49-55, 58, 70, 76-79
Series IX. Asia Foundations
Boxes 59-60
Series X. Philippines
Boxes 61-64
Series XI. Publications: Southeast Asia
Boxes 65-66
Series XII. Cambodia (Laos & Thailand)
Boxes 67-69
Series XIII. Vietnam
Boxes 73-74
Series XIV. Burma
Boxes 74
Series XV. Malaysia, Singapore & Indonesia
Boxes 74-75
Series XVI. Presidential Libraries Series
Boxes 71-72
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Book Manuscript
  - CH. I, II, III- Old Material Unorganized (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CH. II- Genesis of Ind. Nationalist Movement (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CH. V- Revolution (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CH. VI- The Internal Struggle for Power (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CH. VII- War & UN intervention (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CH. VIII (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CH. IX (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CH. X (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CH. XI (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CH. XII (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series II. Subject Files
  - U.S. and SEA- Alumni Talk at Cornell, June 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Amherst Lecture, Apr.17, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kyoto Address, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The U.S. and Sequato- Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Mar. 6, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The New Republic "The Secret War", May 3, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GMcTK testimony on behalf of the Friends Committee on National Legislation before the Subcommittee on Foreign Assistance, Mar. 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Presidential Speech, AAS (Boston), Apr. 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Political Science PENTAGON PAPERS REVIEW (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Friends Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, Nov. 3, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The New Republic "Cutting the U.S. out of SEATO", Oct.13, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Albuquerque Speech, Sept. 9, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Hearings, Feb. 22, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee,Washington, Feb. 22, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Brockport & Mid-Atlantic (AAS), Nov.18 & 29, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sunday Star Ledger (Newark, NJ), Nov. 19, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Washington Star "A Visit to a Heavily Bombed Area", Oct. 22, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - U.S. and SEA: A New Approach, Aug. 28, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - NY Times articles, Oct. 26 & Feb. 10, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Role of U.S. in SEA- Univ. of California Santa Barbara, July 18, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - St. Louis Post-Dispatch and Washington Post articles, Oct. 8 & 20, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - U.S. role in SEA-Singapore, July 3-8, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Le Monde Diplomatique "La Politique Americaine en Asie Du Sud-Est", July 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Le Monde Diplomatique "U.S. role in SEA", May 19, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Claremont College, Apr. 17, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Los Angeles, Feb. 26, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Center "Important New Factors in U.S. Foreign Policy", Mar. 15, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NY Times article, Feb. 10, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Alumni News, Mar. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam and After: What Lessons Have We Learned (Los Angeles), Feb. 26, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "The View From Hanoi" (Santa Barbara), Jan. 20, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Djakarta, Feb. 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica- VIETNAM, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The New Republic- Pieces on Laos, July & Aug. of 1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Mobe "Going Nowhere in Paris", Dec. 26, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Kahin and Porter's "The Administration's Bloodbath Argument", July 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - "The Future of U.S. Policy in SEA", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Four Senators: News Release; Cambodia Invasion, May 15, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Nixon Strategy, June 1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - American Involvement in Vietnam, May 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Smith College, Apr. 14-15, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - McGovern-Laos, Mar. 16, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - The Future of U.S. policy in Southeast Asia (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Fraser & Hatfield Press Release; Cambodian Crisis (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Consequences of the Invasion of Cambodia (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Arts & Sciences Cornell University, Spring 1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Truman Encyclopedia; "Truman and Indochina", 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Lecture Notes, May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Rutgers, Apr. 18, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Cambodia, The Administration's Version and Historical Record (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Washington D.C. AFSC Press Seminar, Dec. 9, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Commentary on Nixon's Address; Cornell University, Nov. 3, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Oct. 15, 1969, Oct. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Oct. 15th Mobilization, Oct. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Shimoda Conference, Sept. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Peace Through Law, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, Apr. 17 & 25, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Washington, D.C., Mar. 28, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NY Times Bloodbath Piece, Dec. 6, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Bloodbath Question, Oct. 20, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rosenthal Conference Statement (Military Budget) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Colorado, Nov. 8, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Cornell Daily Sun, Sept. 16, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The New Republic, Oct. 12, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - South Dakota, Sept. 10, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - News Release by 26 Specialists & NY Times Book Review article, Jan. 7 & Aug. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cazenovia, Dec. 1, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cornell, NYC, Oct. 29, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mo. Council of Churches, Oct. 24, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NLF's Terms for Peace, Oct. 24, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Speech & Cornell-Chicago Conference, Feb. 17 & Oct. 13, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hobart College, Spring 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell, May 24, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bard College; The War in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Emma Willard School; Conference on Southeast Asia, May 13, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - New Hampshire; The War in Vietnam, Mar. 10, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New Orleans, La.; Open Forum on Vietnam, Feb. 5, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University, Feb. 15, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Boston Univ.; Interfaith Seminar for Clergy, Oct. 1, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Alumni News, Sept. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Nasution: Letter, Aug. 23 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Wash. Educational TV debate, Aug. 9, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Times of India editorial, Aug. 4, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The U.S. in Vietnam written by Kahin and Lewis, Jun. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - National Teach-In on Vietnam (Washington D.C.), May 15, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - University Education and Student Life conference, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Unknown group photo, (no date) (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - De Antonio file, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Djokosutono interview, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Van der Plas, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Cosmological Factor - unknown draft, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Secretary Dulles' telephone call to ambassador lodge, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Haggerty diary and telephone call transcripts, 1954-55 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Human Rights and Foreign Policy: The Record of the Carter Administration - draft, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Round Table Conference, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Misc items: memo's, notes, bulletins (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - "A Question of Sovereignty", E. Z. Rodmualdez, no date (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Misc. subject files, 1988-1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Peace - Southeast Asia, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - MDAP material, 1950-1952 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Biog. data on Dutch officials, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Sukarno's visit to U.S., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Moh. Hatta (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - MDAP material, 1950-1952 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Indonesian documents, ca. 1950's (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Dutch newspaper "Mare" on Kahin, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - The Democratic Kampuchea resistace, the Kampuchean countryside, and the Sereikar, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Kahin's notes from Vietnam, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Depatch from the New Zealand Minister in Djakarta, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Misc. figures, charts, graphs (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Min. of Religion materials (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers, 1949-1963 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Security Council - official records, 1949-1950 (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - General Correspondence
    - Trip to Southeast Asia-correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Trip to Southeast Asia-correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Trip to Southeast Asia-correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Trip to Southeast Asia-correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Trip to Southeast Asia-correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - General correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - General correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - General correspondence, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - General correspondence, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - General correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - General correspondence, 1954-60 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - General correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - General correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - General correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - General correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence A-M, Late 79- (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence to Lauriston Sharp (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence to Lauriston Sharp (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence to Lauriston Sharp (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - General correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence (by individual)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1966-71 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - A.F.S.C. (Mike Yarrow) correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A.F.S.C. general correspondence, 1955-72 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Roeslan Abdulgani letters, 1954-63 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cindy Adams letters, 1964-66 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hilman Adil letters, 1956-64 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Drs. Moh. Ali letters, 1959-62 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Gabriel Almond letters, 1955-64 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - John M. Allison (ambassador) letters, 1967-75 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Anak Agung Gde Agung letters, 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Benedict Anderson correspondence and paper (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Benedict Anderson correspondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Benedict Anderson correspondence (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Benedict Anderson miscellaneous materials (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Lindy Aquino correspondence, 1974-76 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Thomas Atkinson correspondence, 1960-69 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Earl of Avon correspondence, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Douglas E. Ashford correspondence, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - General correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Harsja Bachtiar correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - James D. Bell correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Berkley W. Bedell correspondence, 1978-83 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Stanley Bedlington correspondence (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Harry Benda correspondence, 1954-65 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Anthony Barnett correspondence, 1981-84 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Harry Benda correspondence, 1966-71 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John S. Blackton correspondence, 1966-72 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Knight Biggerstaff correspondence, 1954-63 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Harry and Trudy Blair correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Molly Bondan correspondence, 1980-90 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Molly Bondan correspondence continued, 1968-74 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Molly Bondan correspondence continued, 1959-64 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Robert Bone correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Arnold Brackman correspondence, 1955-69 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - John F. Brohm correspondence, 1956-66 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Brookings Institute, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Donald Brown correspondence, 1967-73 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Fred Bunnell correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Fred Bunnell correspondence, 1965-75 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Ali Budiardjo correspondence, 1955-61 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - William P. Bundy correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - John R. Burke correspondence, 1967-69 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Richard Butwell correspondence, 1958-65 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - General correspondence, 1958-65 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - John F. Cady correspondence, 1957-64 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Keith Callard correspondence, 1956-62 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Center for International Studies (Einaudi), 1966-68 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Gerard Chaliand correspondence, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Holly M. Bailey correspondence, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Conference (Spring 1967), 1966-67 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1967-68 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Noam Chomsky correspondence, 1984-86 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hazel Chung, Mar. 20, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Frank Church correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Malcolm Churchill correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Letters to Congress-Indonesian prisoners and Thailand situation, 1972-76 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Compton Boyd correspondence, 1953-65 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Cornell-Cal Matter, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Cornell University Press, 1969-72 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Conrad Cotter correspondence, 1960-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - C.D. Cowan correspondence, 1960-69 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Jeffery Crockett correspondence, 1960-69 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Walter Cronin correspondence, 1957-61 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Pierre Crosson correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Richard D'Amato correspondence, 1966-81 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Louis Damais correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - John Dayton correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Arun Das Gupta correspondence, 1959-64 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Robert Delson correspondence, 1956-62 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Jayshri Deshpande correspondence, 1972-77 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Philippe Devillers correspondence, 1962-75 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Herawati Diah correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dial Press, 1965-70 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Idrus Djajadiningrat correspondence, 1957-67 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Djokosoetono correspondence, 1955-63 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Otto Doering III correspondence, 1961-72 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - John C. Donnell correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - G. Dross and Peggy Duff correspondence, 1968-72 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Tillman Durdin correspondence, 1958-64 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - General correspondence, 1958-65 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - John Echols correspondence, 1955-76 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Essay on John Echols, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Materials on John Echols, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Mario Einaudi correspondence, 1961-63 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Daniel Ellsburg and David Elliot correspondence, 1971-75 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Rupert Emerson correspondence, 1952-65 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1971-66 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Robert H. Estabrook correspondence, 1960-62 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Roger F. Evans correspondence, 1955-63 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - John S. Everton correspondence, 1957-65 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - General correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Charles Fahs correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - John Fairbank correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Howard Federspiel correspondence, 1962-69 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Alexandro Fernandez correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - May Ferrari correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Russell Fifield correspondence, 1957-66 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Larry Finkelstein (Council on Foreign Relations) correspondence, 1955-61 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Herbert Feith & Alejandro M. Fernandez correspondence, 1955-58 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Herbert Feith correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Susan Finch correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Susan Finch correspondence, 1955-63 (Box 76, Folder 20-22)
    - George Fischer correspondence, 1961-64 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Maurice Freedman correspondence, 1965-68 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation, 1966-74 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - J. W. Fulbright correspondence, 1964-74 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 1958-65 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Francis J. Galbraiti correspondence, 1954-74 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dr. Gan Tjong Bing correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - George Gant correspondence, 1956-64 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Paul Gardner correspondence, 1968-71 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hoang van Giau correspondence, 1980-82 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - J.L.R.S. Girling correspondence, 1973-78 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - B. Glassburner correspondence, 1959-62 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Peter Goethals correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Keng Swee Goh correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Frank H. Golay correspondence, 1960-73 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Godfrey & Judge James Gossett correspondence, 1952-68 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Joseph S. Gould & Gene Gregory correspondences, 1963-64 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Jay Gokhale, Robert Hackenburg & Daryl Nyun Han correspondence, 1953-74 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Selig Harrison correspondence, 1970-76 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Harvard University, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Barbara Harvey correspondence, 1969-76 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Alfred Hassler correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Christian Hauswedell correspondence, 1968-77 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Robert Hearn correspondence, 1972-75 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Harold Hinton correspondence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Richard C. Howland correspondence, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Judy & Ali Hudson correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Indonesian-American Society, 1962-68 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - International Voluntary Services, 1962-64 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Yoichi Itagaki correspondence, 1967-75 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Mervyn Jaspan correspondence, 1967-72 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Howard Jones correspondence, 1964-73 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Bernard Kalb, N.L. Kana & George Kanahele correspondence, 1966-71 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Ivan Kats correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Umar Kayam correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - H. K. Khanh correspondence, 1971-74 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Joseph Kraft correspondence, 1966-73 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Owen Lattimore correspondence, 1967-70 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Greg Lavin correspondence, 1972-84 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Don Luce correspondence, 1968-79 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Lim Bian Kie correspondence, 1975-77 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - John Lewis correspondence, 1965-72 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Julia Levtonova correspondence, 1966-73 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Dan Lev correspondence, 1966-77 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - U.S. Economic Aid and the Political Consequence, 1979-92 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Michael Leigh correspondence, 1967-75 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Michael Leifer correspondence, 1965-77 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - John Legge correspondence, 1956-76 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Larry Malley (C.U. Press), 1981-87 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Usha Mahajani correspondence, 1960-75 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Carl Marcy correspondence, 1968-75 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - J.A.C. Mackie correspondence, 1966-77 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Mariani correspondence, 1979-86 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - David Marr correspondence, 1978-91 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - David Marr correspondence, 1971-77 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Gerald S. Maryanov correspondence, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Edward Masters correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Matthew McHugh correspondence, 1978-88 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - George McGovern correspondence, 1964-73 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Stewart Meacham correspondence, 1972-77 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Jonathan Mirsky correspondence, 1967-75 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Soemarsaid Moertono correspondence, 1968-70 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - James W. Morley correspondence, 1982-84 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Wayne Morse correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - David Mozingo correspondence, 1961-80 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - David Mozingo correspondence, 1966-71 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Rudolph Mrazek correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Christine Nabias correspondence, 1970-77 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Akira Nagazumi correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - The New York Times & Bung Natsir correspondence, 1957-72 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Kate Newman correspondence, 1979-86 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Thich Nat Hanh correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Deliar Noer correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Deliar Noer correspondence, 1969-73 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Stanley O'Connor correspondence, 1966-71 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Giok Po Oey correspondence, 1966-76 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Milton Osborne correspondence, 1966-76 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Douglas S. Paauw correspondence, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Roger Paget correspondence, 1966-76 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - L. N. Palar correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Leslie Palmier & Richard L. Park correspondence, 1966-76 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Masashi Nishihara correspondence, 1973-76 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Porter Jobs, 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Gary D. Porter correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - General correspondence, 1967-78 (Box 7, Folder 1)